

(602) 492-7699

<u>9</u>+57 (314) 238-2912

t4da2000@yahoo.com

PORTFOLIO WEBSITE

https://portfolio008.herokuapp.com/

ABOUT ME
ABOUT ME
 Currently utilising Python, Django, HTML, CSS, and Selenium. 12 years of combined .NET (C#), Visual Basic Applications, SQL, & MS Access/Excel support usage. Working knowledge with application/database design through the utilization of SQL 2005, MS Access, MS Visual Basic 6, and MS Excel. Experience in the maintenance, configuration, and troubleshooting various MS desktops and servers. Server and desktop operating system installation and configuration skills which entails: Windows XP, Windows 7, Windows 8, Server 2003, Server 2008 in 32 and 64bit environments.
EXPERIENCE
Global Volunteer / Freelancer Mar 2015 – Current ☐ Extensive traveling to various countries to help impoverished families and children obtain basic computer literacy. ☐ Freelance Software automation tester and Website support.
Software Support Specialist
EDI Health Group
Mar 2007 – Mar 2015
Summary of Duties Performed
 Develop and support EDI document transmissions by utilizing .NET C#, Visual Basic, Web Services, and ASP.NET. Administered an Assessment Tool stored on a SQL server. Designed forms, queries, reports, and charts on the frontend by utilizing Access, Crystal Reports, Excel, and Visual Basic 6. Developed a local database using Access and VBA for issues logging for special projects. Roll out patches on a regular basis with bug-fixes and enhanced features to various Dental Providers. Worked heavily on a project to implement Electronic Credit Card processing and settlements.
Provide phone and email support to various Dental Office Providers Developed and in-house Support personnel.
Access Developer/Database Administrator SmileCare Corporate Office Nov 2002 – Mar 2006
Summary of Duties Performed
Develop and maintain several proprietary databases designed in Visual Basic 6, Access 2000/2003 and SQL 2000 for use by various departments with applications ranging from Credit Card Processing, Digital Imaging, Revenue tracking, Call tracking, Grievance tracking, Adjustments tracking, and Payment tracking.
 Provide ongoing support in Access 97/2000/XP and Excel 97/2000 to the Executive Staff, Accounting Department, Provider Analysis Team, Grievance Department, and Credentialing Department. Run management reports by utilizing Crystal Reports, Excel, and Access on a daily, weekly, and monthly basis.
EDUCATION

John Patterson College